Daeva Azhdaha... Otash!
It's no use.
I guess I just can't...
Stop wasting your time.
Hey, now.
Give that back!
This is more suited for me than you.
I'm sure His Majesty will
tell you the same thing.
Shut your mouth!
Daeva Azhdaha... Otash!
Wha—
See ya, Jahi.
Curse you... Akoman!
THE DEMON KING'S ATTENDANT IS TOO DEPRESSED!!
"The Demon King's Attendant
Is Too Depressed!!"
What am I supposed to do?
Big Sister Jahi.
Lady Doux?
Look, look!
That's a very pretty gem.
I was picking up rocks so no one would
trip on them, and I found this one!
I see.
It's going to be Doux's treasure forever!
Treasure...
A treasure... A treasure-re-re-re-re...
What's wrong, Big Sister?
Something very important
was taken from me.
Something very important to you?
Yes. It's a powerful weapon called an
Ooparts left behind by ancient demons.
And when I had been promoted
to His Majesty's attendant...
You are worthy of this.
He gave it to me.
But that fool Akoman stole it from me.
I've tried to take it back, but he
just keeps getting away from me.
He left me no choice but to report
what happened to the demon king and...
What a flashy lad
overflowing with ambition.
He's a true demon.
He ended up praising him instead.
What am I supposed to do?
Then...
Doux's gonna steal it back!
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait!
That's not necessary, Lady Doux.
What could you possibly gain from
doing such a thing, Lady Doux?
Well, you told me before...
Please listen.
Demons steal, oppress, and kill!
Those are the three
principles we live by!
That's why I'm gonna steal
your important thing back!
Doux can do it!
L-Lady Doux...
Apparently, Akoman is still
asleep. Now is our chance!
Yup, chance.
I wonder if he's bad at cleaning up.
And he's a high-ranking official of
the demon king's army... How pathetic.
I can't seem to find the Ooparts anywhere.
Big Sister, what's this
Oopaoopa look like?
It's Ooparts. It's a large staff,
so if he were to hide it...
It'd probably be under his bed.
All right, Lady Doux.
Will you sneak into his room and retrieve
the Ooparts for me without being seen?
Yup! I'll do my best!
Shh!
Shh.
You must do this quietly,
so he doesn't wake up.
I ended up involving Lady
Doux in a personal matter.
Umph.
But Lady Doux is serious for once.
I cannot ignore her offer...
I'm counting on you, Lady Doux.
Akoman is an expert at
sensing evil or malice.
He'd notice me instantly
if I were to enter the room.
But Lady Doux possesses no evil.
I don't know anyone more fitting for this!
Pardon me!
What are you doing, Lady Doux?!
Well, you're supposed to knock before
going into someone's room, right?
Yes, but you're not supposed
to be found right now,
so you don't need to do that!
Oh, right!
It's just like hide-and-seek.
You must move quickly and quietly
so you don't get caught.
Okay!
Quickly... quietly...
so I don't get caught?!
Lady Doux!
Y-You're all right, Lady Doux.
It doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt.
He's still asleep.
Okay, third time's the charm, Lady Doux.
Okay!
Quickly... Quietly...
Umph.
Very good!
Quickly... Quietly...
Umph.
You don't need to keep saying "Umph."
Quickly... Quietly...
Lady Doux! By your feet! Your feet!
Whoa...
Lady Doux!
Look, Big Sister!
Doux is in a circus!
Lady Doux! Shh! You need to shh!
This isn't good!
Lady Doux has completely
entered play mode.
Lady Doux!
Umph.
Thank goodness.
Hm?
It's all over!
No way!
He hasn't noticed.
Lady Doux, now's your chance!
Please search under his bed.
Okay!
Big Sister!
Lady Doux, did you find it?
I didn't find the staff, but
I found some oohlalapants.
Why are you bringing
something like that over?!
It's smaller than Papa's.
I definitely didn't need to know that!
Hey, what are you sneaking around for?
A-Akoman! Th-This is just, uh...
Big Sister wanted oohlalapants,
so Doux came to steal them.
What?!
You wanted my underwear so
badly you had a kid steal them?
What a perv.
No one wants your underwear!
I came to steal the Oopar... oops.
I figured you were after this.
There's no point in you having it.
You can only use Ooparts when
you're over 500 years old.
How long do you think this thing will
be rotting away before you can use it?
That's why I'm saying that
I'll make actual use of it.
Just give it up already.
Wait!
Oohlalapants.
I knew that... but His
Majesty gave it to me...
So I can't give it up!
Big Sister.
You can have this.
Huh?
Here you go.
B-But Lady Doux, this is
your precious treasure...
Yup.
But I want you to cheer up
even a little, Big Sister.
Lady Doux... But...
Here.
Where did you get that gem?!
Y-Your Majesty?!
Papa!
Jahi! To think I'd find this
gem while looking for you.
Wh-What do you mean?
Well, the incident with the
Ooparts had been on my mind...
I apologize.
Huh?
I apparently caused you some anxiety
because I gave it to you so young.
Your Majesty...
So I wanted to make you
another weapon instead,
and I was looking for a magic stone...
And it's right here!
This is a magic stone?
Ooh!
I'm sure I'll be able to make
something quite powerful with this.
P-Please wait!
That gem is Lady Doux's treasure.
If you're going to do something with it,
it should at least belong to Lady Doux.
Is that right, Doux?
Nope. I already gave it to Big Sister.
I can't possibly take
something so important!
But I want you to cheer up.
I'm just fine!
Even without the oohlalapants?
Oohlalapants?
She means the Ooparts!
That doesn't matter anymore!
What Akoman said is correct.
I can't use it...
But I want you to have
this, Big Sister Jahi.
Lady Doux...
Hm...
Then it can be both of ours.
This treasure can belong to both of us!
Right!
I can't wait to get to work!
What kind of special
effect should I give it?
There's catastrophe, dimensional
confinement, and even stopping time.
N-No, I don't think I need any of those.
Doux wants one that'll
give me lots of snacks!
Snacks, eh?
THE NEXT DAY
What?!
Your Majesty, this is overdoing it.
THE DEMON KING'S ATTENDANT IS TOO TIRED!!
"The Demon King's Attendant
Is Too Tired!!"
Lady Jahi!
There's a misprint in this magical tome.
All right.
Please help us collect
resources to make weapons.
I'll adjust my schedule.
Please train me again!
R-Right...
Please sign this, too.
Please give us a budget.
We don't have enough salt! Oh, the salt!
Th-This isn't good... It's time to
go with Lady Doux on her trial...
Lady Jahi! Lady Jahi! Lady Jahi!
This is my...
room?
Big Sister?
Lady Doux?
Is your fever gone now?
Huh?
You passed out because you had a fever,
so Papa carried you all the way here.
I see...
Have you been taking
care of me, Lady Doux?
Yup! Me and Papa
just made you dinner, too.
He'll bring it soon!
Dinner?
I was asleep for over half the day?!
Thank you, Lady Doux!
But I can't cause anyone any more trouble!
I have to get back to work...
No!
Lady Doux?! Hey, what are you doing?
You have to beddy-bye properly!
That's your trial, Big Sister!
T-Trial?!
A trial to rest until you get all better!
But...
Papa even said it was a great idea.
V-Very well...
Today, Doux is in charge
of taking care of you!
I completely fail as an attendant.
Here you go.
Oh?!
L-Lady Doux, did you
properly wring this out?
Yup. I squeezed it really tight.
But Lady Doux is physically weak...
Er, that's not even the
first problem at hand.
DIRTY RAG
Lady Doux, I have some
towels in my closet...
I'll go get them!
Right here?
Yes. Oh, if you can't reach, I'll...
It's okay! See? It opened.
Lady Doux?!
I-I'm so terribly sorry! I've been so
busy with work that I hadn't cleaned it!
Doux will clean it for you!
Cleaning complete!
A picture book!
Oh, that's a book I used
to read when I was little.
Doux will read it for you!
I'm sure she just wants
to read it for herself.
If you would, then.
Let's see...
Once upon a... Zzz...
She instantly fell asleep?!
H-Hello, Lady Doux?!
You mustn't sleep here!
You'll catch a cold!
Lady Doux...
Are you awake now, Jahi?
Y-Your Majesty...
It's Papa.
Time for dinner.
You got a fever from extreme overwork.
Huh?
If it were something like a cold,
Doux would've healed you by now.
True.
But the only way to cure
overwork is to rest.
That's why Doux stayed by your side
this whole time to take care of you.
I see...
Here!
Eat up!
It's delicious.
Eat lots and get better soon.
GURGLE GURGLE
Here, you should have some, too.
Yummy!
Thank you so much.
I don't know how I can thank
you enough, Your Majesty.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Huh?
Well... You see, I tried to
do your work in your stead.
What?!
And boy, was it a lot...
That was more work than one
should do on their own.
It definitely hit me that we had
given you too much work because
we trust you so much.
So, Jahi, I have redistributed some
of your duties to others.
Even then, I might still have
to give you a lot more work.
And if it becomes too much for you,
I'll find a substitute for Doux's trials.
I've discussed the matter
with Doux as well.
You just rest and think
this over carefully.
Lady Doux.
Doux can wait...
Huh?
Doux will do her best
even if you're gone...
But if that happens, can I come
see you every now and then?
Of course.
Really?!
Okay, you can have this.
SHOULDER MASSOOGE TICKET
This is...
If you get tired again, tell me.
Doux will tap, tap your shoulders.
All right.
SHOULDER MASSOOGE TICKET
She spelled it wrong.
Lady Doux, it's time for today's trial.
Jahi? What are you doing here?!
Is your fever all better?
Yes. I'm surprised myself
at how much better I feel.
You liar!
E-Even if you feel better,
you're still recovering.
You can't work like tha...
Lady Jahi, thank you very much!
As you can see, I finished
everything already.
What?!
Th-That's not good, Jahi!
If you push yourself like that...
It's all right, Your Majesty.
SHOULDER MASSOOGE TICKET
The next time I get tired, I'll have
Lady Doux give me a shoulder massage.
Big Sister!
I'm still going to be
stern with you, Lady Doux.
Okay, got it!
Doux! You don't have a shoulder
massage ticket for me?!
DOUX'S SHOULDER MASSOOGE PARLOR
"SHOULDER MASSOOGER"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: TAKERU TAKEMIYA
SONG: DOUX
Welcome
Hello
Take a load off
We'll get rid of your everyday fatigue
When we get rid of your everyday fatigue
Let's play lots and lots again
Tap tap tap, tap tap tap
Tap tap tap, tappity tap
Shoulder massooges
SHOULDER MASSOOGE TICKET
DOUX'S SHOULDER MASSOOGE PARLOR